Encoded and Released By MgB
Sub Upload Date: October 21, 2015
(MINIONS SINGING "UNIVERSAL
STUDIO'S THEME" IN MINIONESE)
(CHOKES)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(FOLK ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(MINIONS LAUGHING)
(MINIONS WHOOPING)
(YELLING)
(LAUGH AND CHATTER IN MINIONESE)
(GASPS)
NARRATOR: Minions.
Minions have been on this planet
far longer than we have.
They go by many names.
Dave, Carl, Paul, Mike.
(GASPS, YELLS)
Oh, that one is Norbert.
He's an idiot.
They're all different,
but they all share the same goal.
(ALL GASP)
To serve the most despicable
master they could find.
Boss!
(ROARS)
(ALL CHEERING)
Making their master happy was
the tribe's very reason for existence.
But that's not to say
that they didn't have other passions.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(LAUGHS)
Huh?
Finding a boss was easy.
(ALL SCREAMS)
But keeping a boss,
therein lies the rub.
(ROARS)
(CHATTERING IN MINIONESE)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS NERVOUSLY)
(GASPS)
(ALL YELLING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(DINOSAUR GASPS)
(SIGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
(GROANS)
(ROARS)
(SCREAMING)
(ALL GASP)
(ALL CRYING)
(GROANS)
NARRATOR: Nope,
it wasn't easy for these guys.
But they never gave up.
With the emergence
of the Stone Age
came the rise
of a new species.
Man was very different
from the dinosaur.
He was shorter, hairier,
and way, way smarter.
(YELLING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
The Minions took
an instant liking to man,
and helped him
the best they could.
(ROARS)
- (GRUNTS)
- Oh, no, no.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(ALL LAUGHING)
Eh?
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(ROARS)
(SCREAMS)
NARRATOR: Poor man.
So trusting, so fragile.
So, so delicious!
Their quest for a boss
put the Minions front and center
for some of civilization's
most historic moments.
(SPEAKING FAUX EGYPTIAN)
Anubis! (GRUNTS)
NARRATOR: Ancient Egypt
held great promise.
(YELLS IN MINIONESE)
Okay! (GRUNTS) Pancake!
(CROWD SCREAMING)
NARRATOR: But it didn't last long.
Hmm. Oh!
(MUTTERS MINIONESE)
Ow!
The Dark Ages were
actually fun times.
Their new master
had a tendency
to party all night
and sleep all day.
(CLEARS THROAT) Ooh!
(GROANS)
(MINIONS SNICKERING)
(SPEAKS FAUX ROMANIAN)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(YELLS IN MINIONESE)
(SCREAMING)
Oh.
NARRATOR: But eventually,
the party was over.
(BLOWS)
(SNEEZES)
They bounced from
one evil boss to another,
but they never seemed
to find their perfect fit.
(SCREAMS)
(ALL YELLING)
One particular employer
took their failure very, very badly.
(YELLING)
Huh?
The Minions had no other
choice but to keep moving.
(SHUDDERING)
Oh. (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
NARRATOR: And then,
when all hope seemed lost,
they found sanctuary.
The Minions were safe!
(ALL CHEERING)
(SINGING "WE WISH YOU
A MERRY CHRISTMAS" IN MINIONESE)
(LAUGHING)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
- (GRUNTS)
- (ALL LAUGHING)
(YELLING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
NARRATOR: Years passed as the
Minions forged their own civilization.
They truly made
a life for themselves.
But something just wasn't right.
(GRUNTS)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
They felt empty inside.
Without a master,
they had no purpose.
They became aimless
and depressed.
(SINGING "WE WISH YOU
A MERRY CHRISTMAS" SLOWLY IN MINIONESE)
(ALL CRYING)
If this continued any longer,
the Minions would perish.
But all was not lost
for one Minion had a plan.
His name was Kevin.
(GRUNTS)
He was excited to share
his idea with the tribe.
He'd been preparing
for days, weeks, months.
But now he was ready.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(WHIMPERS)
(MUMBLES)
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
(STUTTERS IN MINIONESE)
(ANNOYED GRUNT)
Buddies!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
- NARRATOR: Kevin would leave the cave...
- (ALL GASP)
...go back
to the outside world,
and he would not return
until he had found his tribe
the biggest,
baddest villain to serve.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
But he needed help.
Me!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
NARRATOR: Bob was eager to go,
But Kevin felt he was
just not strong enough
for the dangerous journey ahead.
Uh, no. (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(GASPS)
Luckily, someone stepped up.
- (ALL LAUGHING)
- KEVIN: Stuart!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Huh? Me, me?
Oh! Thank you.
NARRATOR: Truth be told,
Stuart had no idea what he was chosen for...
(GASPS)
...but was thrilled
it made people cheer for him.
- Thank you.
- (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
- (PLAYS GUITAR)
- (SINGS IN MINIONESE)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Me!
(GRUNTING)
(PARTS)
Eh, okay.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(SOBBING)
(SIGHS)
(GASPS)
NARRATOR: Eventually,
Bob's energy and enthusiasm,
but mostly lack of other volunteers,
changed Kevin's mind.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(ALL CHEERING)
The tribe said their farewells.
Kevin had given them something
they hadn't had in a very long time.
Hope.
Bob!
(CHUCKLES)
- Hey, Tony! (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
- (MINIONS CHANTING)
Tom... (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Chris... (SOBBING)
- KEVIN: Hey, Bob.
- (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Oh. (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Bye-bye.
(MINIONS CONTINUE CHANTING)
NARRATOR: Kevin felt pride.
He was going to be
the one to save his tribe.
- Stuart felt hungry mostly.
- (STOMACH RUMBLING)
He was going to be the one
to eat this banana.
(GROANS)
And Bob...
(GASPS)
Bob was frightened
of the journey ahead.
(WHIMPERS)
Ah. Okay.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(WHIMPERING)
(SNIFFS) Okay. Okay.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
NARRATOR: And they were off.
Off to find their new boss!
(KEVIN SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(YELLING)
(BOB SNORING)
(CONTINUES SNORING)
(CHUCKLING)
(BOB PANTING)
BOB: Huh? Kevin!
(PANTING)
(STUART GRUNTING)
(CONTINUES GRUNTING)
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
(GROANS) Huh?
- (STOMACH RUMBLING)
- (WHIMPERS)
(CONVERSING IN MINIONESE)
(GROANS)
Huh? Banana!
Uh, Stuart?
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Banana. Banana!
(BOTH SCREAMS)
- Ugh! Ugh! Stuart!
- (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
- (GRUNTING)
- Stopa!
(GRUNTING)
- (SLURPING)
- Uh, Bob! Stopa!
(GASPS)
Huh? Oh!
(CHEERS)
Bob!
Huh?
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(STUART GRUNTS)
Uh, no, no.
No, no. No, no, no.
(GRUNTS) Profiterole.
(MUFFLED)
(SNICKERS)
No, no, no!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Stuart...
Ah!
(CROWD CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
- (CHEERS)
- (CHUCKLES)
Oh, look at that one!
Whoa!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Peace!
Make love, not war!
Peace and love!
(CHANTING) Boo-ya!
Boo-ya! Boo-ya!
Hey, hey, hey, oh.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Kashmiri?
Boo-ya!
(CHANTING) Boo-ya! Boo-ya!
Oh.
(SIGHS)
Banana! (CHUCKLES)
- WOMAN: Hey! Hey, taxi!
- BOB: Hey! Hey!
Oh.
(CHUCKLES)
BOB: Hey, hey, hey, hey!
- Banana! Hey, hey!
- (YELLS)
(GASPS)
Stuart! Hey, oh!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
- BOB: (YELLING) Kevin!
- (GASPS)
Bob!
(MUFFLED SPEAKING IN MINIONESE)
Oh. Bello!
- (TYRES SCREECH)
- (WOMAN SCREAMING)
- (BOTH PANTING)
- Bob!
(HUMS HAPPILY)
Huh? Oh.
- (GASPS) Ah! Bob!
- (GROANS)
- (PANTING)
- Huh? Whoa!
(CHUCKLES)
(CROWD CHATTERING)
WOMAN: (ON PA) Women's bell bottoms
and tie-dye shirts marked down.
Check out our wide selection
of go-go boots and miniskirts.
(GASPS) Bob!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
- (YELLS)
- (SCREAMS)
(GROANS) Okay.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Huh?
Bob!
WOMAN: (ON PA)
The store is now closing.
Hey, what are you doing?
(SPEAKING MINIONESE) Bob!
- WOMAN: (ON PA) Give me that!
- (KEVIN YELLS)
(GASPS) Kevin!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Oh. Oh.
Ah.
Huh?
(CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLES) Oh.
Oh. Hey!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
...buddies.
No? Oh.
Bob! (GRUNTING) Bob!
Oh. (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Tim.
Oh! (CHUCKLES)
Me Tim!
Mmm, thank you! Hmm?
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(LAUGHING)
(SIGHS)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
...Stuart?
Uh, nah.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Okay, okay.
Oh. "Dating game."
- Okay. (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
- (SLURPING)
And welcome back
to The Dating Game!
Well, Jennifer...
(GIGGLING)
...have you decided
which of these three gentlemen
you'll go on a date with?
Is it Bob?
- (SPUTTERS)
- Yeah! Go, Bob!
HOST: Kevin?
(SPEAKING MINIONESE) Kevin!
HOST: Or will it be Stuart?
Oh. Yo, Stuart!
Gosh! This is so hard!
They all sounded so cute.
Um, I think I'm gonna go with...
(STATIC)
(SCREAMS)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(GRUNTING)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE) Stuart.
WOMEN: (SINGING) VNC!
MAN: You're watching the top-secret
Villain Network Channel.
If you tell anyone, we'll find you.
Huh! (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Sponsored by Villain-Con,
for 89 years straight, the biggest
gathering of criminals anywhere!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Big boss.
Attend guest lectures
from esteemed villains,
make contacts in
the underworld community,
and for the first time anywhere,
Scarlet Overkill!
Evil.
So evil.
(YELLS)
HOST: Criminal genius!
Hey, a girl's gotta
make a living!
- HOST: Move aside, men!
- SCARLET: Make way.
- HOST: There's a new bad man in town...
- SCARLET: Excuse me.
- HOST: ...and that man is a woman!
- (SCARLET CHUCKLES)
HOST: Crime isn't pretty!
It's red hot!
(BOTH SIGHS)
HOST: Get to Villain-Con
this weekend.
Only at 545 Orange Grove Avenue
in Orlando, Florida.
So much fun, it's a crime.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh! Villain-Con, Orlando.
Whoo-hoo!
(CHUCKLES)
Bello! Uh, Orlando?
Ugh. (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Hey, uh...
(SPEAKING MINIONESE) Orlando?
(BARKING)
- Oh, hello.
- (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Orlando?
(BABBLES)
Uh-huh. Ah, okay.
Thank you, baby! Bye-bye!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Ah.
KEVIN: (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Orlando!
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
- Hey, Stuart... (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
- (GROANS)
(HORN HONKS)
Oh, yeah! Far out!
Love is the way, brother!
Ah! (CHUCKLES)
Eh, no, no, no, no, no, Kevin.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Hmm.
(HONKING)
(YELLS)
(LAUGHS)
(IMITATING STUART IN MINIONESE)
(BLOWS RASPBERRY)
(GRUMBLING)
Hey! Stopa! Stopa! Stopa!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(HUMS RIDE OF THE VALKYRIES)
Stopa! Ugh!
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(YELLS)
(SCOFFS)
- Stuart...
- (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(WHIMPERING)
- (TYRES SCREECH)
- (SCREAMS)
(KEVIN COUGHS)
(NERVOUSLY) Oh...
Oh, Walter, look!
These adorable little freaks
are headed to Orlando, too!
Yeah, I see that!
Hey, Walter Junior!
What's happenin'?
- WALTER: Tina.
- Hi!
Binky.
Mmm, mmm.
What do you say we give
these fellows a ride?
BOTH: Yay! New friends!
All aboard the Nelson Express!
You, one-eye!
You're sitting next to me!
- Okay.
- (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
- Stuart!
(CHUCKLES)
(GRUNTS)
(TYRES SCREECH)
Glad we came along before
some weirdos picked you up!
(CHUCKLES)
Who wants apple slices?
Ah, ah! Ooh, ooh!
Oh, you, too!
Growing boy-like creatures
need their strength.
Okay.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Heck, yeah!
(MUNCHING)
- Thanks, man!
- (GRUNTS)
All righty! Who needs
to stretch their legs?
Yeah!
Yes! Me, me, me!
Sweet!
You guys wait here, we'll be right back.
Okay, Nelsons, let's do this!
(CAT MEOWS)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(BLOWS RASPBERRY)
- (ALARM RINGING)
- (WOMEN SCREAMING)
Go, go, go!
- Okey-dokey. On the road again.
- (STARTS ENGINE)
- (REVS ENGINE)
- (TYRES SCREECH)
(GRUNTING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
Dad! We got company!
It's because I tripped
the alarm. I stink!
Hey, we all make mistakes, sugarplum.
You're still learning.
Huh! What?
- Your father's right, Tina.
- WALTER: Reload!
He wasn't this good
at being evil overnight!
WALTER: Reload!
Your time's coming.
(CHUCKLES)
(GROANS) It's jammed!
(SIRENS WAILING)
(TYRES SCREECH)
Huh?
- (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
- (CHUCKLES)
(GASPS)
Okay, who did that?
- Uh... (SPEAKING MINIONESE) Stuart!
- Huh? (STAMMERS)
That was great! (LAUGHS)
(CHUCKLES) Thank you!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Say, fellas, can we get personal
for just a second?
Why are you going to Orlando?
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Come on. You can tell us.
You're going to Villain-Con, aren't you?
- (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
- Villain-Con. (CHUCKLES)
Villain-Con.
Wow! So many bad guys
in the car. What fun!
I knew it! I knew you were villains!
Didn't I, honey?
What a small world!
Hope we're not in rival gangs.
(CHUCKLES)
Binky! Joke! (CHUCKLES)
Babies, huh?
(EXPLODES)
(MINION CHEER LEADER ECHOING)
(CONTINUES CHEERING)
(GRUNTS)
(WHIMPERS)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(GRUNTS)
ALL: Yay.
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
- (SIGHS)
(DAVE SHOUTING EXCITEDLY)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Big boss!
(ALL CHEERING)
(CHANTING)
(DAVE SHUSHING)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(GRUNTS)
(ALL CHEERING)
- (SNORING)
- (MOANS)
(BLOWING)
When we get to Orlando,
I'm gonna get all my favorite
villains to sign my magazine!
Dumo the Sumo!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE) Boss!
Oh, Kevin, you don't wanna work for him!
He ate his last henchmen!
Uh...
TINA: Frankie Fish Lips.
He lives in the ocean.
- (SPEAKING MINIONESE) Boss?
- Oh...
Can you breathe underwater?
Uh, so-so.
(GASPS) Oh, oh, oh!
Look at her!
Scarlet Overkill!
The coolest super-villain,
like, ever!
She started out as your average little girl,
braces, pigtails.
But by the time she was 13,
she built a criminal empire!
If I was a Minion,
that's who I'd want to work for!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE) Oh.
Here we are!
Beautiful Orlando!
Yeah! We're here!
MADGE: Orlando!
Hey, gang, watch this!
MAN: (ON SPEAKERS)Welcome to
Billy Bob's Bait Shop. How can I help you?
Yeah, hi.
Uh... (CLEARS THROAT)
We're here for, uh,
so much fun, it's a crime.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Whoo-hoo! (LAUGHS)
Villain-Con!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(GRUNTING)
All right!
Here we go!
Well, this is it!
I wanna tell you, and I really mean this.
I really appreciate what you did
back there with the cops.
Really!
Dad!
It's Frankie Fish Lips!
(SNIFFS)
I can smell him from here!
WALTER: Junior!
Get my camera!
Good luck in there, boys!
I hope you find what
you're looking for!
ALL: Bye!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(GIGGLES)
Villain-Con!
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah!
Villain-Con!
Whoo!
- KEVIN: Okay!
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Oh! (CHUCKLES)
Any evil talents?
Not bad.
What about you?
Any evil talents?
Uh...
Bello!
La, la, la! La, la, la!
Eh?
That's not evil or a talent.
(GROANS)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(HUMS)
Bello!
(YELLS)
Ha-ha!
No?
I'm sorry! But I'm not looking
for any more servants,
for I, Professor Flux,
have invented
the world's first time machine!
Every time I visit the future,
I bring my future self back to help me.
Hello!
Oh.
Move that over there,
Professor Flux from two weeks from now.
(GROANS) As you can see,
I don't need any help.
(GRUNTS)
Oh, way to go, guys.
We killed the original!
- (GASPS)
- (ALL YELLING)
Please!
Eh... (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(MUTTERING IN MINIONESE)
MALE ANNOUNCER: Villain-Con
presents our keynote speaker,
Scarlet Overkill!
The world's first
female super-villain!
(STAMMERING)
Appearing right now in Hall H!
Bob! Stuart! Buddies! Hey!
Buddies! (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Scarlet?
(STUTTERS) Kevin!
MALE ANNOUNCER: Are you ready...
(ALL CHEERING)
- Yeah!
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...for Scarlet Overkill!
(SCARLET SIGHS)
SCARLET: Doesn't it feel
so good to be bad?
Scarlet! Scarlet! Scarlet!
Yes!
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
(LAUGHS EVILLY)
ALL: Whoa.
(SIGHS)
Whoo-hoo!
(CHUCKLES)
(GRUNTS)
Awesome!
(ALL CHEERING)
Yeah!
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(SIGHS)
Wow! Thank you!
- CROWD: (CHANTING) Scarlet! Scarlet!
- (CHUCKLES)
Thank you so much!
Okay. (SHUSHING)
(CHANTING RECEDES)
Ah.
When I started out,
people said a woman
could never rob
a bank as well as a man!
Well, (IN SING-SONG VOICE) times change!
- (LOUD CHEER)
- I love you, Scarlet!
Look at all those
faces out there!
We are all so different!
But we have one
thing in common.
(GURGLING) We were
born with flippers!
No? Just me? Okay.
(CLEARS THROAT)
We have big dreams!
And we will do anything
to make them come true!
- (CHEERING)
- Have any of you ever dreamt
of working for the greatest
super-villain of all time?
Yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
(ALL CHUCKLE)
(CHUCKLES)
Well, what if
I were to tell you
that I am looking
for new henchmen?
Hey, boss! Boss!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(CHUCKLES)
I truly believe
somewhere out there
is a villain with the potential
to serve greatness!
And it could be any of you.
Whoa!
Although,
let's not kid ourselves.
Truly, the only men for this job
are Kevin and his Minions!
- Huh? But... But...
- SCARLET: Ten times the evil
in half the package!
I am just in awe!
Let's hear it for Kevin.
He saved his tribe!
(CHANTING)
Kevin! Kevin! Kevin!
(CHANTING) Kevin! Kevin! Kevin...
Hey! Kevin. Hey. Hey!
Argh!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
So, how should we
do this? Hmm.
Oh.
You see this
tiny little trinket?
- Well, just take it from my hand and you've got the job.
- (ALL GASP)
(CHUCKLING) No big deal,
it's almost too simple.
Uh...
Oh, come on!
Don't be afraid.
Just take the stone
and get that job! Come on!
Oh, okay.
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...Boss!
That job is mine!
Ooh!
(VILLAIN LAUGHING EVILLY)
(ROARS)
(GROWLS)
(STRAINING)
Now go easy on me.
- (PAINED GRUNTING)
- Whoops! (CHUCKLES)
(YELLING)
Love the costume!
Ha!
Uh...
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
So cool!
(MINIONS YELLING)
Tim? Tim!
(SINISTER CHUCKLING)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING) Uh...
- Oh, no, Bob!
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(CHUCKLING)
Ah! Tim! Tim!
Is no one good enough?
KEVIN: Bob!
(BATTLE CRY)
(GRUNTING)
(INDISTINCT YELLING)
(YELLING)
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- (GURGLES)
VILLAIN: I got it! I got it!
(ALL GRUNTING)
Ah!
Didn't my speech inspire anyone
to rise up and
prove themselves worthy?
All these villains and
yet I still have the bear.
Stuffed bear!
Why am I holding a bear?
- (CROWD MURMUR)
- Who has the ruby?
(BOB GAGGING)
(CROWD GASP)
Wow! Who...
- Who are you, my knights in shining denim?
- (MOANING GRUNT)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...Stuart.
...Bob.
Minions!
That was incredible!
Behold! The last
creatures you'd expect
- to win the day have emerged victorious!
- (MINIONS CHUCKLING)
- Everyone, meet my new henchmen. The Minions!
- (MINIONS CHEERING)
MINIONS: Kumbaya!
Kumbaya! Kumbaya!
Kumbaya!
Hey! (CHUCKLING)
I know those guys! I gave them a ride here!
Whoo-hoo!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Buckle up, boys!
Next stop, England.
(YELLING HAPPILY)
(HUMMING)
- (LINE RINGING)
- (GROANS CONTENTEDLY)
Oh... (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- (PHONE RINGING)
- (PANTING)
(GROWLS)
(COUNTS IN MINIONESE)
(SINGING "MAKE 'EM LAUGH" IN MINIONESE)
(MUMBLING)
(PHONE RINGING)
Bello?
Hey, Kevin! Eh?
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Boss? In England?
Nah, (SPEAKS MINIONESE) Boss!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(SINGING CONTINUES)
(BLOWS INTO TUBA)
(LAUGHS)
(GROANS)
Ah, uh... Bello, Kevin?
(KEVIN GRUNTS)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...England?
- D900D9">(KEVIN SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- Uh-huh. (SPEAKS MINIONESE) ...Boss?
(YETI ROARS)
Scarlet Popapil. Ah.
(MINIONS YELLING)
(ROARING)
(LINE BEEPING)
Bello? Bello!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE) Bello?
Oh!
Wow!
Ah! (GRUNTS)
(WHIMPERS)
Here we go! There.
By the way,
I really like your bear.
Herb! My baby!
You know I am!
How'd it go?
(CHUCKLES)
Were you evil?
So evil!
Oh!
A little bird
dropped this off today.
(HERB WHISPERS MESSAGE)
It's me,
I'm the "H."
Also, there was no bird.
Also me.
Herb, seriously,
I wanna dig up that William Shakespeare
so he can see
what true writing is.
I love it!
Ah, that works out because I love...
(CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLING)
Well, I love... too.
(IMITATING SCARLET AND HERB)
Ah, the love, ah!
- (KISSES) Oh! Oh, ah.
- (LAUGHING)
Oh, boys,
could you come here, please?
Meet my husband, Herb.
Inventor, super genius, fox.
(SIGHS)
Herb, these are
the new recruits.
Kevin, Stuart, and that
cute little one is Bob.
Hey, Bello!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Right on! You guys are crazy
little and way yellow,
And I dig that!
(GRUNTING)
Sweet, man!
- (YELPS)
- Ah, ah.
Whoa! (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
I know, right?
Ah!
SCARLET: Just a few things I
stole to help fill the void.
- Whoa!
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE) ...mega ukulele!
Checkin' out my can?
We stole that
because finally someone
expressed my love of
soup in painting form.
Wow!
Ooh!
Okay, listen up!
It is time to get down to business.
Do you know who this is?
Uh... (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
This is Queen Elizabeth,
ruler of England.
Oh, I love England.
The music, the fashion.
I'm seriously thinking
about overthrowing it someday.
- (GASPS) Ooh!
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Anyway, this pale
drink of water oversees it all.
I'm her biggest fan,
love her work!
And I really, really,
really want her crown.
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- (GIGGLES)
Steal me the crown
and all your dreams come true.
Respect! Power!
Banana!
(CHUCKLES)
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(MINIONS SHUDDERING AND GRUNTING)
- (MUTTERING)
- Ha! (GRUNTS)
Henry!
(STRAINING GRUNTS)
- (GASPS)
- (SHUDDERS)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...England. Uh...
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- nt color="#D900D9">(GROANS)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...England...
(YELPS)
- (GROWLS)
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(SCREAMING AND CHATTERING IN MINIONESE)
(ROARING)
- (LAUGHS)
- (ALL GASPING)
(GROWLING)
(YELLING IN MINIONESE)
Oh, uh...
Hmm.
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Heh.
- (CHUCKLING) Wow!
- KEVIN: Whoa.
Ooh-la-la.
- HERB: No! (CHUCKLING)
- Oh, no.
Don't get too close, boys.
When it's completed,
it'll be my ultimate weapon.
But right now, it's leaking radiation
like you would not believe!
So, you're here for gear.
Whoa!
Bob, Robert, Bobby, my boy.
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- You get my far-out stretch suit.
Wow! (CHUCKLES)
Kevin, Kev-bo,
Seventh Kevin,
you are the proud owner
of my lava lamp gun.
Ah?
This baby shoots actual lava!
Ooh! (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- HERB: Pretty cool, right?
- (CACKLES)
And finally, Stu. Stu-art,
Stu-perman, Beef Stu.
I got you the coolest invention,
probably ever.
(CACKLES) Oh.
Hypno-hat!
Uh, oh.
Uh...
- (BOTH MUTTERS)
- (IMITATES CHICKEN)
You can use it to
hypnotize anyone. Anyone!
Oh, you look so great!
I feel like a proud mama
with three
- dashing evil sons.
- (YELPING)
- Uh, Scarlet, (STAMMERS)
- Scarlet... (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
No, no. Don't say anything.
I won't understand.
It's getting late.
You've had a big day, you must be exhausted!
Boing, boing, boing,
boing, boing...
Wow! These cats
are pumped!
Well, maybe I'll settle them down
with a bedtime story?
- Ha-ha!
- (RAPID GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
How does that sound, Bob?
Bob. Bob! Bob!
Oh! Bedtime porry?
That is a groovy idea!
I'll go get some cookies and warm milk.
This is gonna be so fun!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...bedtime porry.
Oh, yes, I've got a really,
really good bedtime porry.
Once upon a time,
there were three little pigs.
(PIG GRUNTING)
One fateful day, the pigs
encountered a big, bad wolf...
(SNARLS)
...who had a wonderful
surprise for them!
The wolf offered the three
piggies and all their friends
- a job working for her.
- (CHEERING)
Everyone would be so happy!
All the three
little piggies had to do
was just steal one little crown
that the beautiful wolf
had wanted
ever since she was
a penniless little street cub,
unloved and abandoned.
But that crown would mean
she was a princess,
and everybody loves a princess!
So the wolf sent the piggies
to get that crown.
- (GRUNTING)
- (ALARM BLARES)
But the little pigs
weren't up to the challenge.
They failed their mission.
So the wolf huffed and puffed,
and she blew them off the face of the earth!
Yo, po, po!
The end.
(BOTH STUTTER)
Good luck getting
that crown tomorrow, little piggies.
I know you won't disappoint me.
Um.
(SNORES)
KEVIN: Okay.
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE) ...Scarlet.
- (WHIMPERING)
Which way is the loo, please?
Hmm.
Oh, thank you.
Ah.
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(CLEARS THROAT) Bello.
- Uh...
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE) ...please.
You're not allowed in without an adult.
Scram, hooligans!
Oh. (GROANS)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Uh, mm.
(BOB CHUCKLING NERVOUSLY)
Ooh...
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Oh, la...
Stuart... (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- (STUART GROWLS SOFTLY)
- (YELPING)
(KEVIN GRUNTING)
How many tickets, please?
(STUTTERS)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...please.
(KEVIN GRUNTS)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...please.
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- (CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Enjoy yourself, love.
MINIONS: Thank you!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
It was nowhere near Hyde Park!
(CHUCKLES)
Bob's your uncle.
KEVIN: Huh, hmm.
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- STUART: Okay.
- (KEVIN GASPS)
- (BOB HUMS)
- KEVIN: Okay.
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- (KEVIN AND STUART GRUNTING)
- Huh? Ah!
(KEVIN SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- (ALL SIGH IN RELIEF)
- He-hey.
Okay.
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- BEEFEATER: Hey!
- (GASPS)
- What are you doing here?
- (KEVIN STAMMERS)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
This is a restricted area!
Hands in the air!
No... (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(SINGS HAIR IN MINIONESE)
Stop that!
(CONTINUES SINGING)
Get back.
(ALL SINGING HAIR IN MINIONESE)
(CHUCKLES)
Yay!
(GRUNTS) Ah!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Bob, Stuart...
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(CHUCKLING AND CHEERING)
(STRAINING GRUNT)
- (GROANS)
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(CHUCKLES)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
MAN: So...
So, you came for
the Queen's crown, did you?
Well, you're gonna
have to get through me!
The Keeper of the Crown!
(LAUGHING)
(IMITATING KEEPER)
Ow! Hey!
You think it's
funny to mock the elderly, do you?
Uh... (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(GRUNTS)
I've been up here for decades,
just waiting for someone to try
and steal the Queen's treasure!
(GROANS)
Okay.
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(SINGS IN MINIONESE)
What are you saying?
Never mind, don't care!
(LAUGHS)
Oh, no! (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Oh, no, you don't!
(STRAINING AND YELLING)
Oh, flippin' heck!
(KEEPER YELLS)
(MUFFLED) What's goin' on?
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(YELLS)
Bob...
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- Eh... Hmm.
- Wow. (GRUNTS)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(THUDS)
(KEVIN SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(CROWD CHEERING)
(PANTING)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Hello!
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
Huh? (LAUGHS)
(BOTH PANTING)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(CHUCKLES)
(BOB SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(BOTH YELPING)
Hello!
Stone the crows!
Stop him, lads!
Wait!
Go for the legs!
(ALL YELPING)
Gordon Bennett!
Kevin!
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
The Queen's
been kidnapped, Sarge!
Blimey!
(SIRENS WAILING)
Hyah! Hyah!
THE QUEEN: Ooh!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(SCREAMS)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING AND YELLING)
Ha! Boo-ya!
(SCREAMS AND GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
Huh. Hyah! Hyah!
What's going on?
Bello!
Oh, my goodness!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- Whoa!
- Ha-ha! (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
THE QUEEN: No!
(GROANS)
- Gentlemen do not steal ladies' crowns!
- (GRUNTING)
Huh? Hmm?
(RAPID PANTING)
(SCREAMS)
(GASPING AND GRUNTING)
- (HORSE WHINNIES)
- Huh? (GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(SCREAMS)
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
(GRUNTS)
THE QUEEN: Oh, dear!
(SCREAMS)
(BOTH SCREAM)
(STRAINING)
(SCREAMS)
Ah! Ahhh!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Yeah! (LAUGHS)
You scoundrel!
After them! Uh-oh.
(TYRES SCREECHING)
(YELLING)
MAN: Stop the blighter!
(RAPID PANTING)
- Go on, grab him!
- (GASPS)
Huh?
(STRAINING)
(YELLS)
Huh? Oh.
(SINGING)
(GRUNTS)
Cor, blimey!
One of England's most famous
myths has become a reality
as a new king has been crowned.
Bob, who appears to be
a bald, jaundiced child,
has pulled the famed sword
right from its stone,
which, legend dictates,
makes him the new king.
- (SPITS) Tiny yellow traitor!
- (CUP BREAKS)
(GROWLS)
(JOYFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(LAUGHS) England!
ALL: England! England!
(CHANTING) England!
England! England!
(GAGGING) England! England...
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Ha, ha!
(GRUNTS)
(MINIONS SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(ALL YELLING)
(SINGING IN MINIONESE)
(INDISTINCT MUTTERING)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(LAUGHS) Bello!
Bello!
Cut!
(SHUDDERING)
- Hey, Bob. (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- (MUNCHING)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(ALL LAUGH)
(YELLS)
- ROYAL ADVISOR: Hello, King Bob.
- Uh...
Welcome to Buckingham Palace.
Uh, no.
Oh, what's the matter,
Your Majesty?
Whatever's bothering you,
we can make it right.
Just name it!
Oh.
(CHUCKLING) Buddies!
Buddies! Buddies!
Buddies!
(CHUCKLING)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Oh.
(CLEARS THROAT)
- Uh... (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- (FEEDBACK)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(CLEARS THROAT)
King Bob!
(CHEERING)
MAN: Long live the king!
- WOMAN: King Bob!
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...Bob... (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...King...
(BLOWS RASPBERRY)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- (SPUTTERS AND LAUGHS)
- (BOTH LAUGH)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
So... (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(SINGLE SLOW CLAP)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(SIGHS)
King Bob!
(CHEERING)
Oh... Yeah!
(LAUGHS)
BUTLERS: King Bob! Wait!
- Wow!
- BUTLERS: Whoa! (GRUNT)
Whoo-hoo!
(GRUNTS)
(PANTS) Oh...
Yee-haw!
King Bob!
Hyah!
(YELLS IN MINIONESE)
(BATTLE CRY)
Hmm? Huh! Ah!
(CHUCKLES)
- (RINGS BELL)
- (CHUCKLES)
Yes, King Bob. Oh.
- (RINGS BELL)
King Bob?
Ah, Claire.
Mmm, Tiffany.
(SPEAKS MINIONESE) Rawr!
Ball! (GRUNTS)
- How dare you!
- (YELLS)
(MUFFLED GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(GROWLS)
(WHIMPERS)
Scarlet!
Don't you "Scarlet" me,
you backstabbing little traitors!
Using Herb's invention
to steal my crown?
(SHUDDERS)
I feel used.
Not gonna lie.
You stole my dream!
I was going to conquer England someday!
There was gonna be a coronation,
and I was going
to be made Queen.
Every moment was planned.
I'd wear a dress so sparkly,
it glowed!
And everyone who ever
doubted me would be watching,
and they would be crying!
I was going to be
the picture of elegance and class!
And you pinheads screwed it up!
No, no, no!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
No, no, no, King Bob!
You cannot just abdicate the throne!
Who invited the square?
And you definitely cannot just
give the job to this woman!
There are laws!
Boss. (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...Boss.
(LAUGHING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...Scarlet Popapil!
- (SHOCKED MURMURS)
- King Bob has officially changed the law,
Clearing the way
for Scarlet Overkill
to be crowned Queen of England!
She will be coronated
at London's historic Westminster Abbey.
If I wasn't so polite, I'd say this spells
certain doom for the country,
if not the world.
But I'm so very polite
that I shall keep my mouth shut.
(LAUGHS)
But, seriously,
we're all in big trouble.
REPORTERS: Scarlet! Scarlet!
SCARLET: I don't have time
to answer any questions.
I just want to
thank the Minions
for going above and
beyond the call of duty.
You are three tiny, golden...
(GIGGLES)
...pill shaped
miracle workers,
and you have stolen
not just England but my heart.
REPORTER: Scarlet, over here!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
- Pardon me?
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Eh?
Wow! So many!
Good for you!
Well, you'll all
get what you deserve.
(GRUNTS)
Serve! (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...serve!
(ALL EXCLAIM EXCITEDLY)
Whoo-hoo!
(SINGING THEME FROM
"THE MONKEES" IN MINIONESE)
(LAUGHS)
Oh.
Go ahead, go ahead.
- Uh...
- (ALL SHUDDER)
(KEVIN SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- Uh...
- (DOOR PEEPHOLE OPENS)
I don't want you to take this
the wrong way, but I hate you.
I thought I could get over what you did,
but I feel so betrayed.
I think...
Yes, I think we're gonna have to break up.
- And it's not you.
- (SOBS)
Wait, hold on.
It is you. It's 100% you!
(GASPS) No, no.
So get comfortable, Minions.
Get real, real comfortable.
Because this is where
you're going to spend
the rest of your
worthless little lives.
(WHIMPERING)
All right!
Let's do this!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE) Herb!
Who's this handsome "Herb" fella?
No, my name is "Blerb."
I'm a dungeon master.
Prepare for torture,
which I do!
- (ALL GASP)
- (WHIMPERS)
All right, are we comfy?
Doesn't matter! This is torture!
(BOTH SCREAM)
- Huh.
- Oh. (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Wow! Harder than I thought.
Next machine!
Oh, welcome to Hang Town!
Population, you!
(GRUNTS) Oh.
(YELPS)
- (MINIONS LAUGH)
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Whoo-hoo!
Cut it out! This is
really unprofessional!
There's no laughing
in the dungeon!
I wanna see tears and
I wanna hear screams,
or I'm gonna get... Wait!
Hey!
Ooh! I've got a groovy idea!
Ah!
(MINIONS LAUGH)
Look at this!
Argh! (LAUGHS)
(ALL LAUGHING)
SCARLET: Hello!
Will the future king, Herb Overkill,
please come upstairs
to prepare for the coronation?
Well, I hope you learned
your lesson for today.
- (ALL LAUGH)
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
And by the way, it was me,
Herb, the whole time!
I don't even know
anyone named "Blerb"!
Uh, Herb...
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(WHIMPERS)
Oh. Huh.
I am hours away from becoming
the Queen of England!
I know! It's a gas!
(CHUCKLES)
I will finally get my crown.
Yeah.
It's all I've ever wanted.
I'm going to be so happy.
(LAUGHS)
But let me ask you
something, Fabrice.
Does that look like this to you?
(LAUGHS)
Mrs. Overkill, the hair in that picture,
it's just two wavy lines!
Oh, so, what,
now you're an art critic?
I drew that when I was five years old!
Get out of my sight!
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (SCREAMS)
Bye, Fabrice!
I liked him. He was fun.
So, what do you
think of the dress?
Oh, it's so beautiful.
So fashion-forward. So Valentino.
Gave it a sweetheart
neckline because you're my sweetheart.
The high collar
and cinched waist
reflect a simpler,
more violent time.
The material is a blend of taffeta
and high-density body armor.
Fully armed and loaded.
And that glow,
that's nuclear.
Nice. Just one more
thing to do.
Gotta look good for the public.
Ugh.
Do you mind?
My pleasure.
(HERB GRUNTS)
Little tighter, sweetie.
Come on, I can take it.
- Little tighter.
- (GRUNTING LOUDLY)
- Tighter!
- (STRAINING)
Must have tiny waist.
Seeing stars, seeing stars!
(GASPS)
Losing feeling in my legs. Perfect!
Tie it, tie it, tie it, tie it.
(KEVIN SIGHS)
(KEVIN SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Huh?
Ah. Bob! Stuart!
- BOB: Eh?
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- (BOTH GRUNTING)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(CHUCKLES)
Ooh! Bello!
(IN SING-SONG VOICE) Ooh-ooh!
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- (SQUEAKING)
Ah! Oh.
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Ah.
(ALL GRUNT)
Huh!
(ORGAN PLAYING)
(SOBBING AND BLOWING NOSE)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(GRUNTS AND GASPS)
Ah.
(BOTH SPEAK MINIONESE)
- Eh, eh, Kevin...
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE) ...Scarlet.
(GRUNTS)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Ah!
"Porry Scarlet."
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
He, he!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE) ...Boss.
- (GRUNTS)
- (SQUEAKS)
Oh. (GIGGLES)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Ah, okay!
(CHUCKLES)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Huh?
(ALL GRUNT)
(MINIONS SCREAM)
I love you, Scarlet!
Queen wave, queen wave!
Queen waving!
(APPLAUSE)
- I am so, so excited! This is perfect!
- (GIGGLING)
Everyone looks so nice!
Oh! Oh, you are just adorable!
Oh, yes!
- (ORGAN PLAYING)
- And that music, oh!
Who is that organist?
She is good! Right? She looks like an Edna.
Edna, you are very good!
Who was that? Whoa!
(GIGGLES)
- Thanks for doing this, padre. Big fan.
- Uh-huh.
Come here, let me squeeze you!
Oh, you are so squishy!
(KEVIN GRUNTING)
(SIGHS)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...Scarlet.
Go, go, Go!
(GROANS)
(KEVIN GRUNTING)
- (FRUSTRATED GRUNT)
- (CHUCKLES AND SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Ouch! Ouch!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- (KEVIN SPEAKS MINIONESE)
KEVIN: (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...sayonara!
(GROANS)
Ciao...
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(SINGS AULD LANG SYNE IN MINIONESE)
(KEVIN SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Bob...
- (BOB YELLING)
- KEVIN: Stuart!
(GRUNTS AND SPEAKS IN MINIONESE)
(GRUNTING)
Aww! Oo-ooh!
- (SIGHS)
- (GRUNTING)
- Okay! (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- (GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
Oh! Beh...
ARCHBISHOP: Will you to your power
- cause law and justice...
- (GASPS)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...Popapil!
(GRUNTING AND BLOWING)
Oh!
Ah...
Hmm? Ah...
(CRIES)
Huh? Uh... Uh...
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Stopa!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(GRUNTING)
Bah!
(BOTH YELLING)
(BOTH SPEAK MINIONESE AND YELLING)
ARCHBISHOP: In mercy...
No, no, no!
ARCHBISHOP: Do you, Scarlet Overkill...
(BOTH PANTING)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE AND CHUCKLING)
Yeah!
Huh? Oh?
No!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Uh, mmm...
(GRUNTS)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE) ...Bob.
(GRUNTING)
(BOB SPEAKS MINIONESE)
ARCHBISHOP: I proclaim thee,
Scarlet Overkill,
the Queen of England!
Oh! Huh?
(GRUNTING)
- Kevin!
- (NERVOUS CHUCKLE)
Huh?
(GROWLS)
(PEOPLE GASPING)
Scarlet! Scarlet, my queen?
Somebody help me!
Come on, come on!
Lift on two. One, two!
One, two!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(RUMBLING)
Huh?
(PEOPLE GASPING)
Scarlet! You're okay!
He tried to kill me!
Uh, no...
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Villains, this is no longer a coronation!
It is an execution!
- Get them!
- (VILLAINS YELLING)
(SCREAMING)
Whoa, Nelly!
Run, fellas, run!
VILLAIN #1: Come back here, you!
(PANTING)
Ah!
(ROARS)
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- (YELLING)
(SHUDDERING)
- (MOTOR WHIRRING)
- Uh?
(PANICKED CHATTER IN MINIONESE)
(PANICKED YELLING)
(SINISTER YELL)
Hyah!
(PANTING)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Aah!
You're mine!
Stuart, Bob! Uh...
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(MANIACAL LAUGHING)
Oops!
(YELLING)
Oh!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Hey! I got one!
(YELLING)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(LAUGHING)
Tim!
(SIGHS)
(GURGLES)
Huh?
Oh? Aww! Oh!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(CHUCKLES)
Uh? Eh?
- (GROWLING)
- (SCREAMING)
Tim!
Stuart! Bob!
(SIGHS)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Buddies!
MALE VOICE: (OVER SPEAKERS)
Mind the gap.
(MINIONS CHEERING AND CHUCKLING)
Mind the gap!
Mind the gap! Mind the gap!
Mind the gap.
Mind the gap!
VILLAIN #2: He won't get away!
VILLAIN #3: He won't escape us!
(ROWDY CLAMOR)
(GROWLS)
- (QUEEN LAUGHING)
- Huh?
What about this one?
- Why did the queen go to the dentist?
- (STRAINING)
To get her teeth crowned.
- (LAUGHTER)
- Heh! (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Tell us another one, Lizzy!
KEVIN: Uh, uh...
Bello!
(SIGHS) Oh!
It's you.
Everyone, this is one
of the little fellows
who stole the monarchy from me.
And how's that
working out for you?
Uh, Scarlet...
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Oh, yes, yes, I saw what
was going on on the telly.
Uh, telly?
What was meant to
be the coronation of
Scarlet Overkill has
gone terribly wrong as...
SCARLET: Move!
(GROWLING)
Kevin, Kevin,
I know you're out there.
You think you've gotten away?
Well, what do we have here?
Bello!
Oh, my goodness!
Bob? Stuart?
Which one shall I kill first?
Little Bob? Stuart?
Bob! Stuart!
I will do it, Kevin,
if you are not back here by dawn!
Oh, my!
(GASPS) No!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...buddies!
...Scarlet.
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING AND YELLING)
(SIGHS)
(SINISTER LAUGH)
There he is!
(GRUNTING)
Follow me!
(ALL CLAMORING)
Ah! Ha-haa!
(LAUGHS)
Who the man, eh?
Uh... Oh!
- (DISTANT THUDDING)
- Oh.
(YELLING)
Harder! It's just my head.
(SPITS)
- Oh, no!
- (PANICKED GRUNTING)
DUMO THE SUMO: This way! Let's get him!
VILLAIN #2: Go, go, go!
(PANICKED GRUNTING)
- (ROARS)
- (KEVIN YELLING)
No! (YELLS IN MINIONESE)
(NERVOUS GRUNTING AND MOANING)
- (ALARM BLARING)
- Huh?
(SCREAMS)
(CRIES)
Oh.
(NERVOUS CHUCKLE)
(BLOWS) Huh?
- FEMALE VOICE: Ultimate weapon initiated.
- (SCREAMING)
Activation in three, two, one.
(VILLAINS GASPING)
(ECHOING) Bello.
(VILLAINS SCREAMING)
Huh? (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...buddies!
(MUFFLED MUMBLING)
SCARLET: This is it, boys!
Things do not
look good for you.
Oh, and I'm keeping the bear.
(MUFFLED GASPS) Tim!
You're not gonna need him
where you're going.
(WHISPERING) Heaven.
(GROWLING)
(BIRD SQUAWKING)
Huh? Uh... Aah!
Shoosh, shoosh,
shoosh, shoosh! Oh!
Huh? Ah!
(GRUNTING)
Bye-bye. Say bye-bye,
Bob. Bye-bye!
(MUFFLED WHIMPERING)
(SOBBING)
(SCREAMING)
(CHUCKLING)
(BOTH STRAINING AND MUMBLING)
(CHUCKLES)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(BOTH CHEERING)
Huh?
Oh, whoa!
Wait, what? How did he...
(GROWLS) Hold my bear.
(BOTH YELLING)
Huh?
(WHISTLING)
(CHUCKLES AND SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Yippee! Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Kevin!
(GASPS AND SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
So, that's your plan?
Make yourself a bigger target?
(LAUGHS)
(YELLS)
- (CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
- (CHATTERING QUIETLY IN MINICNESE)
(KEVIN WAILS IN MINIONESE)
Huh?
K-K-Kevin? Hey!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...Kevin!
(EXCITED CHATTER IN MINIONESE)
(SCARLET SCREAMING)
Whoa!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(SHUDDERING WHIMPERS)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE) Ow!
And so help me,
I never wanna
see another one of
your goofy, bug-eyed
faces ever again!
- MINIONS: (CHANTING) Scarlet! Scarlet! Scarlet!
- What?
Oh, you've gotta be kidding me!
(ALL SCREAMING)
Oh no, you don't!
Whoa!
And just for the record,
my little deviled eggs,
you can thank Kevin
for what I'm about to do to you!
Ow! Ow!
(SLURPING)
- (ALL CHEERING)
- Bob! Stuart! Buddies!
Tony! (LAUGHS)
Tom!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE) Chris!
You the man!
(LAUGHS) Buddies! Mazel tov.
(CHOKES)
Ugh! Ew!
Ooh! Aah! Kevin! Kevin!
Enough! This ends now!
(GRUNTING)
Kevin!
(LAUGHS) You imbecile!
Have fun exploding!
Baby!
What's the rush?
Got to get out of here!
Let us go!
No, no, no, no!
- (STUTTERING)
- Kevin!
(BOB CRYING)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(SOBBING)
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE)
- (GASPS)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE AND LAUGHS)
(SOBBING)
Kevin...
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(MINIONS HUMMING TAPS)
(ALL HUMMING)
(SCREAMING)
- Huh?
- (EXCITED SPUTTERING)
(CHEERING)
Ha-ha! Whoo-hoo!
(PANICKED GRUNTING AND YELLING)
ALL: Ooh!
(MINIONS CHEERING)
(PAINED CHEERING)
Stuart?
Hmm.
Bob?
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Okay.
(INHALES DEEPLY AND SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(CHEERING AND APPLAUDING)
Ladies and gentlemen, we are here
today to celebrate the Minions!
(CHEERING)
(CHEERS)
- (BARKS)
- Huh! (RETCHES)
The country owes you
a great debt of gratitude.
Bob, you were a wise and
noble king for all of eight hours.
So for you, I offer this tiny crown
for your teddy bear, Tim.
(GIGGLES)
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Oh, very good, Bob!
(SOBBING)
Oh, spectacular!
I'm so proud of you boys!
Oh, Stuart.
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
For you, I have this beautiful,
super-duper, incredible...
Ah!
...snow globe!
Eh? Poglobe?
Uh, ze...
And look, look,
hours of excitement!
Oh, uh...
Yippee.
Uh, eh, gracias.
(SNORTS AND LAUGHS)
Stuart, we're just
messing with you!
Don't be mad at me,
it was Kevin's idea.
Kevin!
(LAUGHING)
THE QUEEN: We have a much
better surprise for you!
- (GASPS)
- (SPEAKS MINIONESE) ...super mega ukulele!
Uh... Wow!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(PLAYING NOTES)
(DISTORTED GUITAR RIFFS)
(CHEERING)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
(STUART SPEAKS MINIONESE)
...poglobe.
Thank you.
Right. Uh...
And finally, Kevin!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
You are a hero of
the highest order.
For your bravery and valor,
I am knighting you.
From here on out,
you are Sir Kevin.
Well done.
(ECSTATIC CHEERING)
MALE NARRATOR: What a beautiful moment!
Kumbaya!
The nation, nay, the world was
celebrating Kevin, Stuart and Bob.
The last few thousand years
were rough, no question,
but things were
finally going their way!
Kevin had never been more proud.
But something was missing.
Yes, good show, good show!
(GASPS)
My crown is gone! It's gone!
Blimey!
She's lost the crown!
Oh, my days!
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
(SINISTER CHUCKLE)
Scarlet?
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Scarlet! Hey!
...Scarlet! Hey!
They took everything from me!
My castle! My reputation!
Things look bleak,
baby, I'm not gonna lie!
But now at least
I have my crown!
(CROWD GASPING)
(GRUNTING)
(MUFFLED) Child,
give me that back.
No, I don't think so!
You have no idea who
you're messing with!
I am the greatest
super-villain of all time!
(CHUCKLES) Oh!
Were you?
(CHUCKLES)
(STUTTERING)
B... B... Buddies...
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Ah!
...Boss! Ha, ha!
Get back! Are you really going
to allow that little penguin
to make off with my crown?
Herb.
I'm done.
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
For me?
Bye-bye!
Big boss!
(MINIONS CHEERING)
MALE NARRATOR: And that is how the Minions
found their new boss.
He was cunning,
he was evil, he was perfect.
He was despicable.
(SINISTER LAUGHTER)
(SHOOING)
(IMITATING)
Huh?
Banana!
- (MINIONS CHATTERING)
- Banana! Banana! Banana!
(SCREAMING)
(YELPS)
Banana!
(GRUNTING)
(LAUGHING)
(HUSHING)
(GROWLING)
Cheese! Cheese! Cheese!
(LAUGHTER)
ALL: Gru! Gru! Gru!
Gru!
(GIGGLING)
(PLAYING ROCK MUSIC)
(SHOUTING)
(SINGING REVOLUTION IN MINIONESE)
Bob...
(SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Hey! Come back here!
(GROWLING)
(ROARING)
- Freeze ray!
- (GUN CLICKS)
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Thanks for Watching , good day :)